Guide to the South Asian Pamphlets Collection, 1920-2005 (bulk 1950-2000) RL.01235
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- India Pamphlets, 1920-2005, bulk 1960-1990, 177 boxes
  - Tourism, 1947-1989, 9 boxes
    - Delwara Jain Temples: Mt. Abu. Rajasthan. Dept. of Tourism. Sirohi, Pedhi, Kalyanji Parmanandji, India: 198-? (Box IN-162)
      Hymns in Marble.
    - Development of Tourist Potential in South India. The Associated Chambers Of Commerce and Industry Of India. New Delhi, India: 1990. (Box IN-162)
      Background paper to be presented at the 'ASSOCHAM-TAAI' Workshop on 19th February 1990 at Taj Coromandel, Madras.
    - Dharamsala: A Little Lhasa in India. Central Tibetan Secretariat. Dharamsala, India: 197-? (Box IN-162)
    - Discover Bombay and the West. India. Dept. of Tourism. Bombay, India: 1973. (Box IN-162)
    - Discover Calcutta and the East. India. Dept. of Tourism. Madras, India: 1973. (Box IN-162)
    - Fairs and Festivals of Haryana. Haryana. Public Relations Dept. Chandigarh, [no publisher], India: 1970? (Box IN-162)
    - Festivals and Fairs. India. Dept. of Tourism. Madras, Department of Tourism, India: 197-? (Box IN-162)
    - Festivals and Fairs. Department of Tourism. Madras, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 196-? (Box IN-162)
    - Festival Dates for 1971 / Full Moon Dates. [n.p.], India: 1970? (Box IN-162)
    - Festivals of Arunachal. Arunachal Pradesh. Directorate of Information and Public Relations. Shillong, India: 197-? (Box IN-162)
    - Festivals of India. India. Ministry of Information & Broadcasting. New Delhi, Publications Division, India: 1968. (Box IN-162)
    - Forgotten Monuments of Delhi And Other Places of Interest with Facts and Fictions. Das, Sukhomoy. New Delhi, Das and Associates, India: 1982? (Box IN-162)
    - Gateway of India: With the Compliments of State Bank of India. India. Dept. of Tourism. India: 197-? (Box IN-162)
    - Glimpses of Cultural Heritage of Himachal Pradesh. Himachal Pradesh. Dept. of Languages and Culture. Simla, Department of Languages and Culture, India: 198-? (Box IN-162)
      Folk dances and folk songs.
    - Glimpses of Goa's History. Goa, Daman and Diu. Dept. of Information. Panjim, Director of Historical Archives, India: 1965. (Box IN-162)
    - Glimpses of India. India. Ministry of Information & Broadcasting. New Delhi, India: 1969. (Box IN-162)
    - Goa Then… and Now. Goa, Daman and Diu. Dept. of Information and Tourism. Panaji, India: 1968. (Box IN-162)
    - Goa. Department of Tourism. New Delhi, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1970. (Box IN-162)
    - Goa. India. Daman and Diu, Panjim, Dept. of Information and Tourism, India: 1961? (Box IN-162)
    - Goa. State Bank of India. Bombay, India: 1964. (Box IN-162)
    - Goa. India. Directorate of Advertising & Visual Publicity. Madras, India: 1964. (Box IN-162)
    - Goa: Daman & Diu. Goa. Dept. of Information and Tourism. Panaji, India: 1967. (Box IN-162)
    - Goa: Land and People. Goa. Dept. of Information and Publicity. Panaji, India: 1987? (Box IN-162)
    - Guide Map of Calcutta & Howrah. Touring Service. Delhi, India: 197-? (Box IN-162)
    - Guide Map of Udaipur. Rajasthan. Dept. of Tourism. Jaipur, India: 1965. (Box IN-162)
    - Guide to Bhubaneswar, Puri, Konarak. Orissa. Home (Public Relations) Dept. Cuttack, India: 1963? (Box IN-162)
    - Guide to Calcutta. Gupta, J. Dutta. Calcutta, National Committee for Geography, India: 1968. (Box IN-162)
      21st Int'l Geographical Congress, India.
    - Guide to Madras. Maps and Atlases Publications (P) Ltd., India: 196-? (Box IN-162)
    - Guide to Poona, A. International Book Service, The. Poona, Dixit, V. N., India: 1966. (Box IN-163)
    - Gujarat Information Centre, New Delhi. Gujarat. Director of Information. Ahmedabad, India: 197-? (Box IN-163)
    - Gujarat: Towards A Self-Reliant Economy. Desai, Hitendra K. Ahmedabad, India: 1967. (Box IN-163)
    - Gwalior: Madhya Pradesh. Madhya Pradesh State Tourism Development Corporation. Bhopal, India: 197-? (Box IN-163)
    - Gwalior: Visit Madhya Pradesh. India. Dept. of Information and Publicity. Gwalior, India: 1962. (Box IN-163)
    - Handbook of India, The. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Kadamtala, India: 1951. (Box IN-163)
    - Hill Resorts of Uttar Pradesh. New Delhi, Aggarwal, Kalpana, Nest & Wings, India: 1972. (Box IN-163)
    - Hill Resorts of Western India. India. Dept. of Tourism. Delhi, Indian Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1973. (Box IN-163)
    - Himachal Calling. Himachal Pradesh. Public Relations Dept. Simla, India: 197-? (Box IN-163)
    - Himachal Pradesh: Cultural Heritage. Himachal Pradesh. Dept. of Education. Simla, India: 1971. (Box IN-163)
    - Himalayan Holiday: Kulu-Manali, Dharamsala, Dalhousie, Ranikhet, Almora, Kasauli, Simla, Mussoorie, Darjeeling, Kalimpong, Kurseong, Nainital. Department of Tourism. Delhi, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1970. (Box IN-163)
    - Himalayan Holidays. India. Dept. of Tourism. New Delhi, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1975. (Box IN-163)
    - Historical Relics of Gour & Pandua. West Bengal. Director of Tourism. Calcutta, India: 1971. (Box IN-163)
    - Holiday Resorts of Himachal Pradesh. Agarwala, Kalpana. New Delhi, Nest & Wings Publication, India: 1966. (Box IN-163)
    - Holiday Resorts of Jammu and Kashmir. Jammu and Kashmir. New Delhi, Nest & Wings Publication, India: 1972. (Box IN-163)
    - Holiday Resorts of Rajasthan. Rajasthan. Directorate of Tourism. New Delhi, Nest & Wings Publication, India: 1972. (Box IN-163)
      A Traveller's Guide.
    - Hotel List: Darjeeling. West Bengal. Director of Tourism. Calcutta, India: 197-? (Box IN-163)
      Guidelines for Foreigners.
    - In the Footsteps of the Buddha. Department of Tourism. New Delhi, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 196-? (Box IN-164)
    - India - Delhi. India. Tourist Office. New Delhi, India: 1973? (Box IN-164)
    - India awaits you with all her charms. India. AIR-India. Bombay, India: 197-? (Box IN-164)
    - India Today: Basic Facts. India. Directorate of Advertising and Visual Publicity. Nasik, India: 1981. (Box IN-164)
    - India Tourism Development Corporation. India Tourism Development Corporation. New Delhi, India: 1969. (Box IN-164)
      Text of the speech delivered by Mr. Romesh Thapar, Chairman, India Tourism Development Corporation at the 4th Annual General Meeting of the Company on 28th Nov, 1969.
    - India. India. Delhi, Information Service of India, India: 1975? (Box IN-164)
    - India. India. Dept. of Tourism. New Delhi, India: 1965. (Box IN-164)
    - India. India. Dept. of Tourism. New Delhi, India: 1970. (Box IN-164)
    - India: A Week in Madras. India. Dept. of Tourism. Calcutta, India: 1965. (Box IN-164)
    - India: Agra. India. Dept. of Tourism. New Delhi, India: 1962. (Box IN-164)
    - India: Complete Guide to the Sub-Continent. India. Dept. of Tourism. New Delhi, India: 1998. (Box IN-164)
    - India: Delhi. India. Dept. of Tourism. Madras, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1973. (Box IN-164)
    - India: Goa. Department of Tourism. [Delhi?], India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1968. (Box IN-164)
    - India: Kanyakumari, Madurai, Tiruchirapalli, Rameswaram, Thanjavur. India. Dept. of Tourism. Delhi, India: 1974. (Box IN-164)
    - India: Kashmir. India. Ministry of Information And Broadcasting. Dept. of Tourism. New Delhi, India: 1962. (Box IN-164)
    - India: Kashmir. India. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Delhi, India: 1966. (Box IN-164)
      Guide to Kashmir.
    - India: Mysore. Indian Tourist Department.Calcutta, India: 1968. (Box IN-164)
    - India: Pune, Nasik, Shirdi. India. Dept. of Tourism. Delhi, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1974. (Box IN-164)
    - India: Tourist Information. India. Dept. of Tourism. New Delhi, India: 1964. (Box IN-164)
    - India: Tourist Information. Department of Tourism. New Delhi, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1970. (Box IN-164)
    - INFA Handy Book For Delhi. Satyajit. New Delhi, INFA Publications, India: 1964. (Box IN-164)
    - Invitation Form Himachal. Himachal Pradesh. Public Relations. New Delhi, India: 1970? (Box IN-164)
    - Island of Diu. Goa, Daman and Diu. Dept. of Information and Tourism. Panaji, India: 1971. (Box IN-164)
    - Isle of Romance: Ranganathittu, The. Mysore. Director of Information and Tourism. Bangalore, India: 197-? (Box IN-164)
      Where The Birds Flock.
    - Jammu and Kashmir: Jammu, Srinagar, Gulmarg, Pahalgam. India. Dept. of Tourism. Delhi, India: 1975. (Box IN-165)
    - Jammu Darshan (A Guide to Jammu). Saraf, Mulk Raj. Jammu, Raj Mahal Publishers, India: 197-? (Box IN-165)
    - Jammu-Kashmir: Jammu, Srinagar city, Gulmarg, Pahalgam, Achabal, Kokarnag. India. Dept. of Tourism. Delhi, India: 1970. (Box IN-165)
    - Kailasanatha Temple, The. Nagaswami, R. [Madras?], State Dept. of Archaeology, Govt. of Tamilnadu, India: 1969. (Box IN-165)
    - Kapaleeswar Temple, Mylapore, Madras: With the compliments of State Bank of India. India. Dept. of Tourism. [n.p.], India: 197-? (Box IN-165)
    - Kashmir. India. Dept. of Tourism. New Delhi, India: 1962. (Box IN-165)
    - Kashmir: Seven Days In The Emperor's Dream Garden. India. Dept. of Tourism. Madras, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 196-? (Box IN-165)
    - Kerala, 1972. Kerala. Dept. of Public Relations. Kottayam, Southern Publishers, India: 1972. (Box IN-165)
      A Comprehensive Reference Book and Tourists' Encyclopaedia.
    - Kerala. India. Directorate of Advertising and Visual Publicity. Calcutta, India: 1966. (Box IN-165)
    - Kerala: Cochin, Kalady, Periyar Wild Life Sanctuary, Quilon, Trivandrum. India. Dept. of Tourism. New Delhi, India: 1970. (Box IN-165)
    - Khajuraho. India. New Delhi, India: 1962. (Box IN-165)
    - Khajuraho. Lal, Kanwar. Delhi, India: 1962. (Box IN-165)
    - Know Your City: Pune. Gogate, V. N. Pune, India: 1989. (Box IN-165)
    - Konarka. Vijayatunga, J. New Delhi, Publications Division, India: 1963. (Box IN-165)
    - Konarka. Orissa. Home (Public Relations) Dept. Bhubaneswar, India: 197-? (Box IN-165)
    - Ladakh. India. Publications Division. Delhi, India: 1965. (Box IN-165)
    - Madhya Pradesh: Bagh Caves, Bhopal, Gwalior, Indore, Jabalpur, Kanha National Park, Khajuraho, Mandu, Pachmarhi, Sanchi, Shivpuri, Ujjain. Department of Tourism. Delhi, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1970. (Box IN-166)
    - Madhya Pradesh: It's Got a Lot More, a Lot Closer Than You Think. Madhya Pradesh Tourism. Bhopal, India: 197-? (Box IN-166)
    - Madhya Pradesh: The Very Heart of India. Madhya Pradesh. State Tourism Development Corporation Limited. Faridabad, India: 1982. (Box IN-166)
    - Madras City Tourist Guide. Tamil Nadu. Madras, India: 1968. (Box IN-166)
      A Map of Madras City attached.
    - Madras. India. Dept. of Tourism. Calcutta, India: 1975. (Box IN-166)
    - Madurai-Rameswaram-Thanjavur-Tiruchirapalli. Department of Tourism. New Delhi, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1970. (Box IN-166)
    - Mahabaleshwar. Bombay, India: 197-? (Box IN-166)
      The Resort Wrapped In Nature's Romance.
    - Maharashtra: Places of Interest. Maharashtra. Directorate of Tourism. Poona, India: 197-? (Box IN-166)
      Publication No.2.
    - Mamallapuram. Ramaswamy, Nalattinputtur Singaperumal. [Madras?], State Dept. of Archaeology, Govt. of Tamilnadu, India: 1969. (Box IN-166)
    - Matheran. Bombay, India: 197-? (Box IN-166)
      Bombay's Nearest Hill Station.
    - Meet Madras: Madumalai Forest. Srinivas, Krishna. Madras, [no publisher], India: 1973. (Box IN-166)
    - Meghalaya: Some Facts and Figures. Barthakur, Pulin Behari. Shillong, India: 1973. (Box IN-166)
    - Mussoorie and the Doon Valley. Narain, K. R. Delhi, [no publisher], India: 1961. (Box IN-166)
      With a foreword by Mr Justice G.D. Khosla.
    - Mysore - A Tourist Treasure. Mysore. Director of Information and Tourism. Bangalore, India: 197-? (Box IN-166)
    - Mysore: Aihole, Badami, Bandipur, Bangalore, Belur, Bijapur, Halebid, Hampi, Jog Falls, Mangalore, Mysore, Pattadkal, Sravanabelagola, Sringeri, Tungabhadra Dam. Department of Tourism. Delhi, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1970. (Box IN-166)
    - Mysore: Land of Charm. Mysore. Director of Information and Tourism. Bangalore, India: 1970? (Box IN-166)
    - Mysore's Cultural Heritage. Mysore. Director of Information and Tourism. Bangalore, India: 1969. (Box IN-166)
    - Nagaland - A Retrospect. Nagaland. Directorate of Information and Publicity. Kohima, India: 196-? (Box IN-166)
    - Nagaland: 1963-1969. Directorate of Information and Publicity, Nagaland. Kohima, India: 1969? (Box IN-166)
    - Nagaland: The First Decade, 1963-73. Nagaland. Directorate of Information, Publicity & Tourism. Kohima, India: 1973. (Box IN-166)
    - Nalrajargarh: A Fortification Lost in Jungle. Gupta, P. C. Das. Calcutta, Directorate of Archaeology, West Bengal State, India: 1968. (Box IN-166)
    - Namakkal Caves, The. Dehejia, Vidya. [Madras?], State Dept. of Archaeology, Govt. of Tamilnadu, India: 1969. (Box IN-166)
    - North-East Frontier, The. Sykes, Marjorie. Varanasi, Sarva Seva Sangh Prakashan, India: 1963. (Box IN-166)
    - Northern Hill Districts of West Bengal. India. Publications Division. New Delhi, India: 1971. (Box IN-166)
    - Ooty. Madras. Director of Information and Publicity. Madras, India: 1966. (Box IN-167)
    - Orissa - Dhenkanal: Kapilas, Joranda, Tikarpada, Talcher. Orissa. Tourism Dept. Cuttack, India: 197-? (Box IN-167)
    - Orissa - District of Sundargarh. Orissa. Tourism Dept. Cuttack, India: 197-? (Box IN-167)
    - Orissa - Ganjam: Chilika, Gopalpur, Taptapani. Orissa. Tourism Dept. Cuttack, India: 197-? (Box IN-167)
    - Orissa - Koraput: Gupteswar, Nandapur, Duduma, Balimela, Sunabeda. Orissa. Tourism Dept. Cuttack, India: 197-? (Box IN-167)
    - Orissa - Sambalpur: Hirakud, Badrama, Nrusinghanath. Orissa. Tourism Dept. Cuttack, India: 197-? (Box IN-167)
    - Orissa at a Glance. Mohanty, Akshaya Kumar.Bhubaneshwar, India: 1981. (Box IN-167)
    - Orissa Invites you. Orissa. Tourism Dept. Cuttack, India: 1978. (Box IN-167)
    - Orissa Tourism: District of Phukbani. Orissa. Cuttack, India: 1981. (Box IN-167)
    - Orissa Tourism: Places of Interest in the District of Keonjhar. Orissa. Tourism Dept. Cuttack, India: 197-? (Box IN-167)
    - Orissa: A Tourist Handbook. Orissa. Home (Public Relations) Dept. Bhubaneshwar, India: 197-? (Box IN-167)
    - Orissa: Koraput (Gupteswar, Nandapur, Duduma, Balimela, Sunabeda). Orissa. Cuttack, India: 1971. (Box IN-167)
    - Orissa: Mayurbhanj, Simlipal, Khiching, Haripur. Orissa. Cuttack, India: 1971. (Box IN-167)
    - Orissa: Sambalpur, Hirakud, Badrama, Nrusinghanath. Orissa. Cuttack, India: 1971. (Box IN-167)
    - Pachmarhi - A Trekker's Paradise. Madhya Pradesh. Information and Publicity. Bhopal, India: 1962. (Box IN-167)
    - Palitana. Gujarat. Directorate of Information. Ahmedabad, India: 197-? (Box IN-167)
    - Pavagadh. Gujarat. Directorate of Information. Ahmedabad, India: 197-? (Box IN-167)
    - Pictorial Handbook of Kerala. Govt. of Kerala. Department of Public Relations. Trivandrum, India: 1972. (Box IN-167)
    - Places of Interest in the District of Puri. Orissa. Tourism Dept. Cuttack, India: 197-? (Box IN-167)
    - Pocket Guide of Tamil Nadu. Tamil Nadu. Madras, India: 196-? (Box IN-167)
    - Point to Point. Burmah-Shell. Delhi, India: 196-? (Box IN-167)
    - Pondicherry: Then and Now. Pondicherry. Home (Information, Publicity and Tourism) Dept. Pondicherry, India: 1970? (Box IN-167)
    - Profile of Bihar, A. Sinha, Shashi Shekhar. Patna, Raj Prakashan, India: 1984. (Box IN-167)
    - Proposals for the Setting Up of Memorials to Commemorate Shri Guru Gobind Singh's Birth Ter-Centenary - 1967. Shri Guru Gobind Singh Foundation. New Delhi, India: 1967. (Box IN-167)
    - Puri. Orissa. Home (Public Relations) Dept. Cuttack, India: 197-? (Box IN-167)
    - Rajasthan: Ajmer, Alwar, Bharatpur, Bikaner, Bundi, Chittorgarh, Jaipur, Jodhpur, Kotah, Mount Abu, Udaipur. Department of Tourism. New Delhi, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1970. (Box IN-167)
    - Rajasthan by Rail and Road. Rajasthan. Dept. of Tourism. Jaipur, India: 196-? (Box IN-167)
    - Rajasthan: Chittorgarh. Rajasthan. Dept. of Tourism. Jaipur, India: 1965. (Box IN-167)
    - Rajasthan: Guide Map of Bikaner. Rajasthan. Dept. of Tourism. Jaipur, India: 1967. (Box IN-167)
    - Rajasthan: Guide Map of Jaipur. Rajasthan. Dept. of Tourism. Jaipur, India: 1966. (Box IN-167)
    - Rajasthan: Tourist Map of Rajasthan. Rajasthan. Directorate of Tourism. Jaipur, India: 1967. (Box IN-167)
    - Red Fort: With the Compliments Of State Bank Of India. State Bank Of India. New Delhi, India: 1973. (Box IN-167)
      Map of Delhi.
    - Review of Activities of the Department of Information and Tourism During 1969-70 and 1970-71. Mysore. Director of Information and Tourism. Mysore, India: 1971. (Box IN-167)
    - Rock-Cute Temples of Kerala. Kerala. Dept. of Public Relations. Trivandrum, India: 196-? (Box IN-167)
    - Route Guide For Hill Resorts of Northern India. Touring Service. Delhi, India: 197-? (Box IN-167)
    - Seminary Hill Forest Park: Nagpur. Nagpur Forest Division, Maharashtra State. Bombay, India: 196-? (Box IN-168)
    - Shillong: At a Glance. Meghalaya. Directorate of Tourism. Shillong, India: 197-? (Box IN-168)
    - Sidi Sayyid's Mosque, Ahmedabad: With the Compliments of State Bank of India. India. Dept. of Tourism. [n.p.], India: 197-? (Box IN-168)
    - South India Hill Resorts: Kodaikanal, Ootacamund, Coonoor, Kotagiri, Nandi Hill. Department of Tourism. Delhi, India Tourism Development Corporation. India: 1970. (Box IN-168)
    - Spotlight on Gujarat. Associated Journals Ltd. New Delhi, India: 1981. (Box IN-168)
    - Stories in Stone. Educational Resources Centre. New Delhi, The University of the State of New York, India: 1966. (Box IN-168)
    - Sun Temple of Konarka, The. India. Publications Division. New Delhi, India: 1963. (Box IN-168)
    - Tamil Nadu at a Glance, 1972. Tamil Nadu. Director of Information and Public Relations. [Tamil Nadu], India: 1972. (Box IN-168)
    - Temples of Goa. Goa, Daman and Diu. Dept. of Information and Tourism. Panaji, India: 197-? (Box IN-168)
    - Terracottas of Antpur, The. West Bengal. Directorate of Archaeology. Calcutta, India: 1966. (Box IN-168)
    - Terracottas of Hetampur, The. West Bengal. Directorate of Archaeology. Calcutta, India: 1966. (Box IN-168)
    - This Is India. India. Dept. of Tourism. Calcutta, India: 1972. (Box IN-168)
    - Tourism and Goan Culture. Institute of Social Sciences. New Delhi, India: 1987. (Box IN-168)
      Report of a seminar. (ISS Pamphlet Series No.3).
    - Tourism in Orissa. Tripathi, P. Cuttack, Home (Public Relations & Tourism) Dept., India: 1971. (Box IN-168)
    - Tourism Policy of Government of India. India. Lok Sabha Secretariat. New Delhi, India: 1985. (Box IN-168)
    - Tourism Policy. India. Ministry of Tourism. New Delhi, India: 1982. (Box IN-168)
      Presented by the Minister of Tourism in Lok Sabha and Rajya Sabha on November 3, 1982.
    - Tourist Guide of Kumaon Region. Nest and Wings. New Delhi, India: 1963? (Box IN-168)
    - Tourist Map of Madhya Pradesh. Madhya Pradesh. New Delhi, Nest and Wings, India: 196-? (Box IN-168)
    - Tourist Map of Tamil Nadu: The State with a Smile. India. New Delhi, India: 1981. (Box IN-168)
    - Tourists' Assam. Assam. Tourism Dept. New Delhi, India: 196-? (Box IN-168)
    - Tourist's Guide Map & Directory of Assam. Assam. Tourism Dept. Guwahati, India: 198-? (Box IN-168)
    - Traveller's Map Of India. Tamil Nadu Tourism Development Corporation Ltd. Madras, India: 198-? (Box IN-168)
    - Treks in Tehri Garhwal. Uttar Pradesh. Bureau of Agriculture Information. Singh, Kunwar Naresh, India: 196-? (Box IN-168)
    - Tribal Panorama. Meghalaya. Agricultural Information Wing, Directorate of Agriculture. Shillong, India: 1979. (Box IN-168)
    - Ujjain. Madhya Pradesh. Information and Publicity. Gwalior, India: 1962. (Box IN-168)
    - Vajreshwari. Maharashtra. Directorate of Tourism. Bombay, India: 196-? (Box IN-168)
    - Varanasi, Patna, Gaya, Older than Legend. India. Dept. of Tourism. New Delhi, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1975. (Box IN-168)
    - Varanasi. India. Dept. of Tourism. New Delhi, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1965. (Box IN-168)
    - Vishnupur. West Bengal Tourism Development Corporation. Calcutta, India: 1981. (Box IN-168)
    - Weekend Trips: Ajanta, Ellora, Aurangabad, Daulatabad. Maharashtra. Directorate of Tourism. Bombay, India: 197-? (Box IN-168)
      Scheme For Low-Income Group Tourists.
    - Welcome to Bangalore - Mysore. Mysore. Int'l Commission on Irrigation and Drainage. Bangalore, India: 1966. (Box IN-168)
    - Welcome to Madhya Pradesh. Madhya Pradesh. Directorate of Information and Publicity. Bhopal, India: 1967. (Box IN-168)
    - Welcome to Punjab. India. Dept. of Tourism. New Delhi, Ministry of Information and Broadcasting, India: 1964. (Box IN-168)
    - When the Wheels Roll on the Grand Road. Orissa Tourism. Cuttack, India: 1980. (Box IN-168)
    - Where to Buy: Agra, Aurangabad, Bangalore, Bombay, Calcutta, Cochin, Delhi, Jaipur, Madras, Mysore, Varanasi. Department of Tourism. New Delhi, India Tourism Development Corporation, India: 1970. (Box IN-168)
    - Yapahuwa. Fernando, W. B. Marcus. Ceylon, Archaeological Dept., India: 1969. (Box IN-168)
  - Transportation, 1961-1990, 1 box
    The 36 pamphlets in this section were published primarily by government agencies, and offer information on regional infrastructure plans, domestic and international transportation and transportation by road, rail, air and water. This section also includes fifteen reports on railway accidents.
    - Agreement between Govt. of India and the Federal Republic of Germany. India. Ministry of Civil Aviation. New Delhi, India: 1965. (Box IN-169)
      Relating to Air Services, signed at New Delhi on 31st May 1963.
    - Agreement between Govt. of India and the Imperial Govt. of Iran. India. Ministry of Tourism & Civil Aviation. New Delhi, India: 1965. (Box IN-169)
      For Air Services signed at Tehran on 10th August 1960.
    - Agreement between the Government of India and His Majesty's Government of Nepal relating to Air Services. India. Ministry of Transport & Aviation. New Delhi,India: 1965. (Box IN-169)
      Signed at New Delhi on 26th November, 1964.
    - Agreement between the Government of India and the Government of the Republic of Lebanon relating to air services. India. Ministry of Transport & Aviation. New Delhi, India: 1966. (Box IN-169)
      Signed at Beirut on 19th September, 1964.
    - Agreement between the Govt. of India and the Govt. of the Commonwealth of Australia. India. Ministry of Transport & Communications. New Delhi, India: 1960. (Box IN-169)
      Relating to Air Services.
    - Agreement between the Govt. of India and the Govt. of the Hungarian People's Republic relating to air services. India. Ministry of Tourism & Civil Aviation. New Delhi, India: 1966. (Box IN-169)
    - Air Travel in India - Safety and Service. Mahajan, Vijay, and Sen, Alka, and Kini, R. N. Bombay, Forum of Free Enterprise, India: 1990. (Box IN-169)
    - Development of Roads in Haryana. Haryana.Chandigrah, Govt. of Haryana, India: 197-? (Box IN-169)
    - Development of Roads in Mysore State. Mysore. Public Works Dept. Mysore, Public Works Dept., India: 1964. (Box IN-169)
    - Extension of Transport Facilities in Jammu & Kashmir. Directorate of Information, Publication Division. Srinagar, Directorate of Information, Publicity Division, India: 198-? (Box IN-169)